=No.9 Hunter=
=Episode 12=
Oh.
To go deeper into the Wilds of Lize,
we must pass through Greed, Wrath,
Obsession, and Hate.
Then Doubt, Envy, Pride, Fear, and more.
Most Hunters only make it
past the first few.
One Yuanzhen disciple made it
to the Envy Gate.
(Ah!)
If only there were a shortcut
straight to the deepest part.
(Dream on.)
If such a path existed,
why would Xuanwu Sect
go through all that trouble
to host the Grand Demon Hunt?
Rumor does say there is one gate
that leads straight
to the deepest depths.
But its difficulty
surpasses all nine gates combined.
Though no one has ever found it.
(Why do I feel like)
(I have been here before?)
Awooo!
(What did this demon come from?)
(He's a Taoist from the human realm.)
(His spiritual energy is so rich!)
(Perfect for restoring my Essence.)
Ah!
(I can't hold back.)
(So this is where it is.)
(Why does this feel so familiar?)
(What a delicious young Taoist, hehehe.)
(What a strange little demon.)
(Hehe...
she's not that scary after all.)
Hehehe.
(So in this lifetime,)
(we still met long ago.)
(Once you step in,
there is no turning back.)
Once you step in,
there is no turning back.
You only get one chance.
If this fails...
Ziyan, if this fails,
I will surely...
With me here, we won't fail.
(The Stone is hidden in the deepest part
of the Wilds of Lize.)
(And within the Wilds of Lize,)
(there're
Sixty‑four Heavenly Stem labyrinths.)
(Dangers lurk within.)
(If you can get the Five Spirits Pendant
from Xuanwu Sect,)
(it can take you directly)
(to the deepest part.)
I need to borrow your pendant.
What good is this betrothal...
I mean, family heirloom?
Ah?
Ah!
(Once you step in,
there is no turning back.)
(Into the Pale Realm.)
(Where one)
(must choose.)
(This place...)
(why does it look exactly like
the young Taoist's dreams?)
(The Four Symbols
govern fortune and misfortune.)
(What's past is done.)
(The four of them
are trapped in the mirrors.)
(This will reveal their true hearts.)
(Stripped of pretense,)
(of masks,)
(their honest feelings toward you.)
"Junior"? Please.
Just being polite.
I only have one Junior.
One more mouth means more food wasted.
You eat like you've never seen food.
Look at the amount you put away.
You're nothing but a burden.
And you have no shame.
Say that again and I will hit you.
Hmph.
What "goddess"?
You do not deserve that title.
You're just a pretty little plaything
for the moment.
I'll have my way with you
sooner or later.
You dirty pervert!
I'll slap you silly!
Demoness.
Go on.
Keep pretending.
I saw through your disguise
from the start.
The moment you slip up,
I'll tear you apart.
I'll destroy your very soul.
So what? Hmph.
(Now it is your turn.)
(Young Taoist.)
You are a demoness
sent to seduce and corrupt me.
Anything inhuman
is an abomination.
As a Taoist,
it is my duty to slay you
before you harm more people.
Slay me? Fine.
Let's see who eats who first.
Pesky Taoist.
Tch!
(To break this illusion and survive,)
(you must choose one of the four mirrors
and kill the person inside.)
(Only if he dies can you live.)
(Only if he dies)
(can you live.)
You don't actually think
I'm that stupid, do you?
That's old news in the Demon Realm.
And you're still using it?
Everything here is an illusion.
Even I am just a mirror image.
If I can break myself,
the game is over, right?
Hey, you.
You should get out more
and see the world.
Next time, come up with something
more creative and fun.
I don't have time for this.
Phew.
Finally made it out.
They would
make the same choice I did, right?
(No. Why can't I use my spells?)
(I need to go back and get them out.)
(Stab yourselves with your swords.)
(Die to live.)
(That breaks the illusion.)
(Yuanchu.)
(What happened to you?)
(Yuanchu,)
(can you hear me?)
(Yuanchu, what is wrong?)
(To break
the Thousand-Fold Love Ordeal,)
(you must kill the one you love.)
(This is Yuanchu's illusion.)
(At a time like this,)
(he is still thinking about that woman.)
This pesky Taoist,
what a player.
How is this possible?
I never expected...
the person
in his Thousand-Fold Love Ordeal
has always been me.
Yuanchu, wake up!
Yuanchu!
Wake up!
Yuanchu, wake up!
You are amazing, Ziyan.
Figuring out how to break the illusion.
Thankfully, goddess,
we all survived.
Ziyan,
are you okay?
I'm fine.
But I feel completely drained.
And I tried using my spells,
but nothing works.
Could it be
the illusion drained my power?
Whoever set this trap
wanted us to trade our power
for our lives.
Our spiritual energy
is probably feeding him now.
We trained so hard for this power...
What do we do now?
Hmm.
I checked each of your meridians.
Your Spirit Roots are intact.
It's only temporary.
Hmm.
Given this situation,
we need to find a safe place
and figure out our next move.
Hmm.
Ziyan,
I heard the Divine Stone
can elevate anyone to godhood overnight.
Once I find it,
I will give it to you.
(You will either kill me)
(or use me to mend the sky.)
(Either way, I am dead.)
(What am I hesitating for?)
(What am I holding on to?)
Here you come.
(Such overwhelming demonic power...)
(so strong it makes me want to flee.)
♪I drink the rain of this mortal world,
and seek the path I chose♪
♪How much sorrow and joy have I known?♪
♪With this flesh and blood,
I chase the distant light♪
♪Just to see clearly
the memories of this drifting life♪
♪Let the wind sweep away
this heavy air of sorrow♪
♪Do not forget the tangled paths
that you and I have crossed♪
♪Let towering waves come crashing down;
I'll fight against the tide♪
♪I shatter the hollow fate
they wrote for me♪
♪With a heart free of regret,
I'll face the heavens and earth♪